export const Data = [
  {
    question: "Can i use my bonus airtime?",
    answer: "Jesus Christ, no !!! üòÇ",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Would the airtime you recharge be the same exact amount in your wallet?",
    answer:
      "For every airtime deposit you make, you get an equivalent Zeddcoin (ZCN) 100NGN AIRTIME is equal to 1 ZEDD COIN(ZCN) üî•",
  },
  {
    question: "What is ZCN / zedd coin?",
    answer:
      "ZEDD COIN(ZCN) is Zeddpays currency , your deposits are converted to zeddcoin and you make purchases with it too ‚ù§Ô∏è",
  },
  {
    question: "What can i purchase with ZCN?",
    answer: "Currently you can purchase 100 Items on Zeddpay with ZCN ü§Ø",
  },
  {
    question: "VPN, Urgh how , why ?? üò§",
    answer:
      "You DONT need a VPN to use Zeddpay, how ever most purchases on zeddpay are US items that are not offered in Nigeria, once you purchase you will get a reedem code registered in the United states, to use this code on a service like spotify, you will have to turn on a VPN(which hides your current location) then you can change your location to the United states, after that, turn off your VPN and you can proceed ‚ú®",
  },
  {
    question: "I am stuck üò≠ , what should i do ?",
    answer: "calm down, we got you! tweet at us @zeddpay ‚ú®",
  },
  {
    question: "To Change your MTN Share PIN",
    answer:
      "Send an SMS with your Default PIN & New PIN & New PIN to 777. For example, send an SMS with ‚Äò0000 1234 1234‚Äô to 777. You can also change your PIN by dialing 777*Default PIN*New PIN New PIN# on your phone and then click on send/press ok. For example, dial *777*0000*1234*1234# and then send/OK.",
  },
  {
    question: "To Change your Glo Share PIN",
    answer:
      "As a new Glo User, your default transfer PIN is 00000. To change this default PIN, dial 132*00000[New PIN][New PIN]#. Example: when you intend to change your default pin and you want your new PIN to be 33222, then dial *132*00000*33222*33222. Once done your default pin will be reset to the new PIN.",
  },
  {
    question: "To Change your Airtel Share PIN",
    answer:
      "The default PIN is used if this is your first time to transfer credit on Airtel. You can change the default pin by sending a text in the following format to 432: PIN 5555 to 432, E.g., to change the password to 4321, the text sent will read ‚Äî PIN 1234 4321 to 432. You will then receive an SMS confirmation from 432.",
  },
  {
    question: "To Change your 9mobile Share PIN",
    answer:
      "kindly dial 247 old pin* and new pin#. For example *247*0000*2222# and press ‚Äúsend‚Äù. To change your Etisalat/9mobile transfer pin is quite similar to the airtime method, dial the following combination *247*old pin*new pin# and send.",
  },
];
